That do it Hello Hello Hi
Good morning everyone today is
day number 14 of our space and
this is the second question of the day so you
guys must be seeing it on the screen so
once we go through what is the question
after that all of you please answer it by
going to our site on this side so the question is
now like this ramp into your car
reminder damages to the number you will so the
question is now in this mixture options I will say out of that
you guys can answer the most favorite
answer and the right answer you think so
travel options option take note of the
details of the I will do the next option A option
BB
torch light with now zikar and demand money
for repairs option C Ramesh Kumar on to the
bike price revenge and option D drive
at high speed changing by pressing
I have given you four options out of these whichever one is the
ride and most appropriate answer you
can select on subscribe you have the
chance  You can get this victory by subscribing on Thursday and
see, I will repeat once again, the
question is 11, if a biker
comes behind your car suddenly and your bumper gets damaged,
then what will you do, option 1 is that
you will take the details of that person's bike and will get a
complaint filed against him
and will claim it for your bumper,
option 2 is you will
fight with the biker and take money from him to get the car repaired,
option 3 is you will take
revenge on that biker and option
4 is you will check the bike at speed, so let me
tell you four options, whichever option you
think you can go and answer on our side
and Chinese beach and for this question,
any three people will randomly select the beach, those three
people can subscribe, by doing this,
our question was also in the morning,
today there will be three more questions at 1
pm and 5 pm, so you can take a total of 15 minutes in all of them as well,
we have the whole day  People
will do it in tonight's show which will be at 10:00,
you can also watch that on our channel live TV,
this is question 6, total 75
questions,
so this is our final tomorrow, so you
still have a chance, if you have not
tried, then you can do a trial and
till tomorrow you have a chance to participate in this lead score and
win, let's
start the question again,
question 60, now mention this remedy entry
government causing minor damages problem,
you will have the option to take note of the details of the
law complaint, unlock fight with, now worry and
demand for the racer car to The Amazing
driver's speech, I will
repeat it once again in Hindi also, a biker gets
stuck
behind your car, so what will you do,
option you will take the details of the bike and
claim this BCD, you will fight the bike car, you will
take SIM money for the reports to get the
car repaired  Option C you will
hit his bike with your own car to
take revenge for this you
will reverse the bike at such a speed so I think a
very clear answer is coming in front of you
which is correct and oh no you all are also
looking at the same answer so do that
you can
go to our site as quickly as possible and take part in some options
and test your digit and the correct
question and submit it,
if you watch it on YouTube then you will
get its link on the description of YouTube, you
can forward it by pressing this link, you
can submit it to Pushp Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal